Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIII: Helen Henslee Doctorow
  - Subseries A: Correspondence
    - Bacchus Fine Foods, undated (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Bacon, Paul, undated (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Baker, Mary Ann And Norman, undated (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Bancroft, Cathy, undated (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Banks, Barbara, undated (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Bark, Earl, undated (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Richard Ward Baxter Contractor, undated (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Bazelon, Cecile, undated (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Beacher, Melvin, undated (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Beasley, Henryetta, undated (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Bedford Hills Free Library, undated (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, undated (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Bender, Sue, undated (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Bergman, Alan and Marilyn, undated (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Berney, Alice and Arthur, undated (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Berry-Hill Galleries, Inc., undated (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Betts, Emilie W., undated (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - The Biggerstaffs, undated (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Biggs, Ellen, undated (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Black, Susanne And Gene, undated (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Blanton, Leonard, Vivian and Bobby, undated (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, undated (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Bookmark, undated (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Borgenicht Gallery, undated (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Boston University, undated (Box 64, Folder 45)
    - Brandt, Arthur, Veronika, Daria, undated (Box 64, Folder 46)
    - Bray, David, undated (Box 64, Folder 47)
    - Brichto, Milly, undated (Box 64, Folder 48)
    - The Bridgehampton Sun, undated (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - Bronx Conservatory of Music, undated (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - Buck Rose, undated (Box 64, Folder 51)
    - Buckley, Gail and Kevin, undated (Box 64, Folder 52)
    - Buckley-Little Book Catalogue, undated (Box 64, Folder 53)
    - Byrne, Charles, undated (Box 64, Folder 54)
    - Cafritz, Conrad and Peggy, undated (Box 64, Folder 55)
    - Cambell, Margaret, undated (Box 64, Folder 56)
    - Candee, Mildred, undated (Box 64, Folder 57)
    - Canio Books, undated (Box 64, Folder 58)
    - Canney, Elizabeth, undated (Box 64, Folder 59)
    - Caparo, Joe and Betty, undated (Box 64, Folder 60)
    - Capp, Robbie, undated (Box 64, Folder 61)
    - Carlow College, undated (Box 64, Folder 62)
    - Caro, Bob, undated (Box 64, Folder 63)
    - Carroll, David, undated (Box 64, Folder 64)
    - Carter, Linda and Arthur, undated (Box 64, Folder 65)
    - Central Falls, undated (Box 64, Folder 66)
    - Chajet, Bonnie and Clive, undated (Box 64, Folder 67)
    - Charles, Nancy and Keith, undated (Box 64, Folder 68)
    - Chazen, Rita, undated (Box 64, Folder 69)
    - Chwatsky, Ann and Howard, undated (Box 64, Folder 70)
    - Ciotti, Russ, undated (Box 64, Folder 71)
    - Cizmar, Paula, undated (Box 64, Folder 72)
    - Clinton, Bill and Hillary Rodham, undated (Box 64, Folder 73)
    - Close, Glenn, undated (Box 64, Folder 74)
    - Coffey, Eleanor, undated (Box 64, Folder 75)
    - Cohn, Sam and Julia, undated (Box 64, Folder 76)
    - Coleman, Jane, undated (Box 64, Folder 77)
    - Colorknits, Inc., undated (Box 64, Folder 78)
    - Columbia Theater Associates Alumna, undated (Box 64, Folder 79)
    - Columbia University, undated (Box 64, Folder 80)
    - Committee for Common Sense, undated (Box 64, Folder 81)
    - Conroy, Maggie and Frank, undated (Box 64, Folder 82)
    - Contemporary Authors, undated (Box 64, Folder 83)
    - Cooper, Jane, undated (Box 64, Folder 84)
    - Corman, Judy and Avery, undated (Box 64, Folder 85)
    - Crabber's Eve Garden Design, Ltd., undated (Box 64, Folder 86)
    - Dash, Robert, undated (Box 64, Folder 87)
    - Davis, Paul, undated (Box 64, Folder 88)
    - de Menil, Christophe, undated (Box 64, Folder 89)
    - Deaton, Ruth, undated (Box 64, Folder 90)
    - Debreczeni, Julia, undated (Box 64, Folder 91)
    - Denzenberg, Tinka, undated (Box 64, Folder 92)
    - Dicterow, Glenn and Karen, undated (Box 64, Folder 93)
    - Dimension Cable Services, undated (Box 64, Folder 94)
    - Doctorow, Caroline, undated (Box 64, Folder 95)
    - Doctorow, E. L., undated (Box 64, Folder 96)
    - Doctorow, Elly, undated (Box 64, Folder 97)
    - Doctorow, Jenny and Jim Fairbrother, undated (Box 64, Folder 98)
    - Doctorow, Lisa and Jon, undated (Box 64, Folder 99)
    - Doctorow, Richard, undated (Box 64, Folder 100)
    - Donovan, Arlene, undated (Box 64, Folder 101)
    - Doubleday, undated (Box 64, Folder 102)
    - Drabinsky, Garth, undated (Box 64, Folder 103)
    - DuBoff, Robyn, undated (Box 64, Folder 104)
    - Dubow, Barbara and Arthur, undated (Box 64, Folder 105)
    - Duffy, James and Martha, undated (Box 64, Folder 106)
    - The East Hampton Star, undated (Box 64, Folder 107)
    - Eastern Suffolk School of Music, undated (Box 64, Folder 108)
    - Edwards, Sandra, undated (Box 64, Folder 109)
    - Ephron, Nora and Nick Pileggi, undated (Box 64, Folder 110)
    - Fairbrother, Janet, undated (Box 64, Folder 111)
    - Farkas, Michael, undated (Box 64, Folder 112)
    - Fasanella, Mary and Marc, undated (Box 64, Folder 113)
    - Finegan, Jackie, Pat, Andrew, Mike, Sonya, Paula, Catherine, undated (Box 64, Folder 114)
    - Fletcher, Christian, undated (Box 64, Folder 115)
    - Fosse, Bob, undated (Box 64, Folder 116)
    - Francis, Richard, undated (Box 64, Folder 117)
    - Frank, Pearl, undated (Box 64, Folder 118)
    - Frazier, L. D., undated (Box 64, Folder 119)
    - Friedan, Betty, undated (Box 64, Folder 120)
    - Friedman,______, undated (Box 64, Folder 121)
    - Fritts, Debbie, undated (Box 64, Folder 122)
    - Gallery A, undated (Box 64, Folder 123)
    - The Gallery at the Water Mill Museum, undated (Box 64, Folder 124)
    - Gelb, Alan and Meriden, undated (Box 64, Folder 125)
    - Gelfman, Jane, undated (Box 64, Folder 126)
    - Gerberg, Mort, undated (Box 64, Folder 127)
    - Gibson, Robert, undated (Box 64, Folder 128)
    - Gilbey, Emma, undated (Box 64, Folder 129)
    - Girl Scouts of Westchester, undated (Box 64, Folder 130)
    - Gittelson, Celia, undated (Box 64, Folder 131)
    - Glucksman, Lewis and Loretta, undated (Box 64, Folder 132)
    - Godwin, Gail, undated (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Goetchius, Millie, undated (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Goff, Lee and Bill Holzman, undated (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Goforth, Susan and David, undated (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Gold, Arthur and Robert Fizdale, undated (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Goldsmith, Barbara, undated (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Goldstein, Rhonda, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Greenberg, Alissa and Sung Lee, undated (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Greenberg, Georgia Shreve, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Greenberg, Marilyn, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Greenberg, Melanie and Lawrence, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Greenberg, Ron, undated (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Greenberg, Steven and Deb Rossow, undated (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Gregorian, Claire, undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Grey, Joel, undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Gronstedt, Dorle, undated (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, undated (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Handman, Bobbie and Wynn, undated (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Hanson, Blake, undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Harbourfront, undated (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Harper & Row Publishers, undated (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Heller, Joseph, undated (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Henderson, Genie, Bill and Lilly, undated (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Herder, Addie, undated (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Hite, Robert, undated (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Hitesman, Cathy and Jim, undated (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Holden, William, undated (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston, undated (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Hope, Judith, undated (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Hoppe, Joanne, undated (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Honk, Pat, undated (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Hudson River Gallery, undated (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Huggins, Mr. and Mrs. Hastings, undated (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Hughes, Jon, undated (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Hughes, Victoria and Bob, undated (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Humane Society of the United States, undated (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Hume, Charity, undated (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - Hunter, Mary Vann, undated (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Inghram, Rose, undated (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Inside Oz, undated (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Irving, John, undated (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Isaacson, Cathy and Walter, undated (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Israel, William, undated (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - Jackson, Bonnie and Michael, undated (Box 65, Folder 44)
    - Jacobson, Elaine, undated (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - Jaffe,_____, undated (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - Jameson Advertising, Inc., undated (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - Jaroff, Gloria, undated (Box 65, Folder 48)
    - Jeffers, Suzie and Charles, undated (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - Jennings, Peter and Kati, undated (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - Jensen, Ea and Jim Brown, undated (Box 65, Folder 51)
    - John Jermain Memorial Library, undated (Box 65, Folder 52)
    - Joh, Monika, undated (Box 65, Folder 53)
    - Johnston, Augusta, undated (Box 65, Folder 54)
    - Jones, Suzanne, undated (Box 65, Folder 55)
    - Jordan, Mary Kathryn and Charlie, undated (Box 65, Folder 56)
    - Jupiter Symphony of New York, Inc., undated (Box 65, Folder 57)
    - Kachalsky, Marty, undated (Box 65, Folder 58)
    - Kasin, Helen, undated (Box 65, Folder 59)
    - Kaufman, Elaine and Joe, undated (Box 65, Folder 60)
    - Kelley, Buncy, undated (Box 65, Folder 61)
    - Keneally, Thomas, undated (Box 65, Folder 62)
    - Kennedy, Eleanore, undated (Box 65, Folder 63)
    - Kent, Adam, undated (Box 65, Folder 64)
    - Kenyon Review, undated (Box 65, Folder 65)
    - Keilson, Gail and David, undated (Box 65, Folder 66)
    - Kiger, Phylicia and Walter Johnston, undated (Box 65, Folder 67)
    - Kingsley, Joyce, undated (Box 65, Folder 68)
    - Klugman, Susan and Billy, undated (Box 65, Folder 69)
    - Koenig, Maria, undated (Box 65, Folder 70)
    - Kossodo, Verena, undated (Box 65, Folder 71)
    - Kraft, Polly, undated (Box 65, Folder 72)
    - Krebs, Ruth, undated (Box 65, Folder 73)
    - Kyle, Betty, undated (Box 65, Folder 74)
    - Labalme, Patsy, undated (Box 65, Folder 75)
    - La Farge, Annik, undated (Box 65, Folder 76)
    - Lail, Jack, undated (Box 65, Folder 77)
    - Landmarks at Risk, undated (Box 65, Folder 78)
    - Lanxner, Kate, undated (Box 65, Folder 79)
    - The Lawyers Committee for Human Rights, undated (Box 65, Folder 80)
    - Lear, Norman, undated (Box 65, Folder 81)
    - LeRoy, Warner and Kay, undated (Box 65, Folder 82)
    - Levine, Elizabeth, undated (Box 65, Folder 83)
    - Levine, Marcella and Paul, undated (Box 65, Folder 84)
    - Levine, Richard, undated (Box 65, Folder 85)
    - Levitas, Mitchel, undated (Box 65, Folder 86)
    - Levy, Helen and Norman, undated (Box 65, Folder 87)
    - Libin, Claire, undated (Box 65, Folder 88)
    - Library Journal, undated (Box 65, Folder 89)
    - Lipman-Wulf, Peter and Barbara, undated (Box 65, Folder 89A.)
    - Lipper, Kenneth and Evy, undated (Box 65, Folder 90)
    - Little Red School House, undated (Box 65, Folder 91)
    - The Loggias, undated (Box 65, Folder 92)
    - The Louisville Review, undated (Box 65, Folder 93)
    - Lowndes, Susan, undated (Box 65, Folder 94)
    - Luers, William, undated (Box 65, Folder 95)
    - Lukerman, Eugenia, undated (Box 65, Folder 96)
    - Lumet, Sidney, undated (Box 65, Folder 97)
    - Luria-Sukenick, Lynn, undated (Box 65, Folder 98)
    - Maas, Peter, undated (Box 65, Folder 99)
    - MacArthur, Renée and Rick, undated (Box 65, Folder 100)
    - McCall's, undated (Box 65, Folder 101)
    - Machlis, Joe, undated (Box 65, Folder 102)
    - McMullan, Kate and Jim, undated (Box 65, Folder 103)
    - Mailer, Norman, undated (Box 65, Folder 104)
    - Manhattan Vision Associates, undated (Box 65, Folder 105)
    - Matthiessen, Maria and Peter, undated (Box 65, Folder 106)
    - Memorial Hospital Blood Bank, undated (Box 65, Folder 107)
    - Merser, Cheryl, undated (Box 65, Folder 108)
    - Michael, Walt and Connie, undated (Box 65, Folder 109)
    - Mississippi Review, undated (Box 65, Folder 110)
    - Montemarano, Dan, undated (Box 65, Folder 111)
    - Montgomery, Henriette and Bob, undated (Box 65, Folder 112)
    - Montgomery, Susie, undated (Box 65, Folder 113)
    - Morell, Gay, undated (Box 65, Folder 114)
    - Morell-Hartford, Lulu, undated (Box 65, Folder 115)
    - William Morrow & Company, undated (Box 65, Folder 116)
    - Ms., undated (Box 65, Folder 117)
    - Murphy, Barbara and Bill, undated (Box 65, Folder 118)
    - Navasky, Annie and Victor, undated (Box 65, Folder 119)
    - New York Public Library, undated (Box 65, Folder 120)
    - New Rochelle Public Library, undated (Box 65, Folder 121)
    - New York University, undated (Box 65, Folder 122)
    - The New Yorker, undated (Box 65, Folder 123)
    - Newhouse, Jeanne, undated (Box 65, Folder 124)
    - Newman, Paul and Joanne, undated (Box 65, Folder 125)
    - Newman, Phyllis and Adolphe Green, undated (Box 65, Folder 126)
    - W. W. Norton & Company, undated (Box 65, Folder 127)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, undated (Box 65, Folder 128)
    - Offit, Sidney, undated (Box 65, Folder 129)
    - O'Keefe, Nancy, undated (Box 65, Folder 130)
    - Olds, Sharon, undated (Box 65, Folder 131)
    - Oliver, Joan, undated (Box 65, Folder 132)
    - O'Neill, Catherine, undated (Box 65, Folder 133)
    - Owen, Jim, undated (Box 65, Folder 134)
    - Pacchiana, Elaine, Doug, and Jeanne, undated (Box 65, Folder 135)
    - The Pace Gallery, undated (Box 65, Folder 136)
    - Thomas Paine National Historical Association, undated (Box 65, Folder 137)
    - Pakula, Hannah, undated (Box 65, Folder 138)
    - Palin, Robert, undated (Box 65, Folder 139)
    - William Pall Fine Arts, undated (Box 65, Folder 140)
    - Palmer, Sandra, undated (Box 65, Folder 141)
    - Papaleo, Joe and Tonie, undated (Box 65, Folder 142)
    - Park and Recreation Association of Sag Harbor, undated (Box 65, Folder 143)
    - Parrish, Kate and Robert, undated (Box 65, Folder 144)
    - Patterson, Jennifer, undated (Box 65, Folder 145)
    - Pearce, David, undated (Box 65, Folder 146)
    - PEN American Center, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Penan, David, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - People for the American Way, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Perkel, Jane, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Petrie, Donald, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Philharmonia Virtuosi, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - The Piano Man, undated (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Pintauro, Joe, undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Planned Parenthood, undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Ploughshares, undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Poets & Writers, Inc., undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Pousette-Dart, Richard, undated (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Powell, Hall, undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Prigmore, Suzette, undated (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Prince Arthur Galleries, undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Prudential-Bache Securities, Inc., undated (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Public Theater, undated (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Pump, Anne and Detlef, undated (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Quinn, Sally, undated (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Rancho La Puerta, undated (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Random House, undated (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Raship, Virginia, undated (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - The Rattrays, undated (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Redbook, undated (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Riordan, Nancy, undated (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Ritchie, Elisavietta, undated (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Ritz Thrift Shop, undated (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Robbins, Yasuko and Gerald, undated (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Rodriquez, Abraham, undated (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Rose, Daniel and Joanna, undated (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Rosen, Elaine and Michael, undated (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Rosenblum, Sylvia, undated (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Rosenwald, Nina, undated (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Rossow, Deb and Steven, undated (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Rubin, Baum, Levin, Constant & Friedman, undated (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Runge, Annelie, undated (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Russell, John, undated (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Sadovnikoff, Laura, undated (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Gloria Safier, Inc., undated (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Sarah Lawrence College, undated (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Sawyer, Lois, undated (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Saxon, Shelly, undated (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Scanlon, John and Julienne, undated (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, undated (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Schneiderman, Anne and Paul, undated (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Schneiderman, Audrey and Howard, undated (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - Schoenfeld, Pat, undated (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - Schwartz, Peri, undated (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Schwartz-Goodman,_____, undated (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons (Lisa Miles), undated (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - Setzer, William and Evelyn, undated (Box 66, Folder 51)
    - Sheehy, Gail, undated (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - Sherry, Dorothy, undated (Box 66, Folder 53)
    - Shreve, Susan, undated (Box 66, Folder 54)
    - Silberman, Ellen, undated (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - Silver, Ken, undated (Box 66, Folder 56)
    - Simon & Schuster, Inc., undated (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Simon, Paul, undated (Box 66, Folder 58)
    - Small, Claire, undated (Box 66, Folder 59)
    - Smith, Dennis, undated (Box 66, Folder 60)
    - Smith, Jean and Steve, undated (Box 66, Folder 61)
    - Smith, Lawrence, undated (Box 66, Folder 62)
    - William Smith College, undated (Box 66, Folder 63)
    - Solomon, Helen and Gary / Cynthia Gains, undated (Box 66, Folder 64)
    - Soloway, Kay, undated (Box 66, Folder 65)
    - Sonet, Ellen and Steven, undated (Box 66, Folder 66)
    - Sound and Hudson Against Atomic Development, undated (Box 66, Folder 67)
    - Southampton, Town of-, undated (Box 66, Folder 68)
    - The Southern Review, undated (Box 66, Folder 69)
    - Stanton, Arthur and Joan, undated (Box 66, Folder 70)
    - Stein, Frankie, undated (Box 66, Folder 71)
    - Steinbeck, Elaine (Mrs. John Steinbeck), undated (Box 66, Folder 72)
    - Steinberg, Joan, undated (Box 66, Folder 73)
    - Stern, Naomie, undated (Box 66, Folder 74)
    - Steibel Modern, undated (Box 66, Folder 75)
    - Strausberg, Susan and Marc, undated (Box 66, Folder 76)
    - Stubbs, Horace, undated (Box 66, Folder 77)
    - Stuttering Resource Foundation, undated (Box 66, Folder 78)
    - Styron, William and Rose, undated (Box 66, Folder 79)
    - Suburban Sanitation, Inc., undated (Box 66, Folder 80)
    - Tager, Tristan, undated (Box 66, Folder 81)
    - Teirstein, Andy, undated (Box 66, Folder 82)
    - Thorne, Joan Vail, undated (Box 66, Folder 83)
    - Time Limousine Service, undated (Box 66, Folder 84)
    - Toscanini, Elaine, undated (Box 66, Folder 85)
    - Touger, Michael and Margaret, undated (Box 66, Folder 86)
    - Turner, Alice, undated (Box 66, Folder 87)
    - Turney, Clayton, undated (Box 66, Folder 88)
    - Tyler, Anne, undated (Box 66, Folder 89)
    - Tyler Graphics Ltd., undated (Box 66, Folder 90)
    - Tyshkov, Michael and Marsha, undated (Box 66, Folder 91)
    - Unger, Rusty, undated (Box 66, Folder 92)
    - United Way, undated (Box 66, Folder 93)
    - U.S. International Communication Agency, undated (Box 66, Folder 94)
    - USA Today, undated (Box 66, Folder 95)
    - Verdon, Gwen, undated (Box 66, Folder 96)
    - Vonnegut, Kurt and Jill Krementz, undated (Box 66, Folder 97)
    - Wachsman, Sam, undated (Box 66, Folder 98)
    - Wallace & Shiel Agency, undated (Box 66, Folder 99)
    - Wallace, Stacey, undated (Box 66, Folder 100)
    - Walton, David, undated (Box 66, Folder 101)
    - Walton, Tony and Gen LeRoy, undated (Box 66, Folder 102)
    - Walz, Kevin and Barbara, undated (Box 66, Folder 103)
    - William B. Ward Elementary School, undated (Box 66, Folder 104)
    - Weinrub, Susan and Steven, undated (Box 66, Folder 105)
    - Wentworth, Jean and Kenneth, undated (Box 66, Folder 106)
    - Westchester County Board of Education, undated (Box 66, Folder 107)
    - White Plains Public Library, undated (Box 66, Folder 108)
    - Whitener, William, undated (Box 66, Folder 109)
    - Sibyl Wild, Inc., undated (Box 66, Folder 110)
    - Williams, Galen, undated (Box 66, Folder 111)
    - Wilson, Andrea, undated (Box 66, Folder 112)
    - Woman's Project, undated (Box 66, Folder 113)
    - The Writers' Workshop, undated (Box 66, Folder 114)
    - Wunsch Art Gallery, undated (Box 66, Folder 115)
    - WVOX, undated (Box 66, Folder 116)
    - YM & YMCA of Mid-Westchester, undated (Box 66, Folder 117)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, undated (Box 66, Folder 118)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, undated (Box 66, Folder 119)
    - Unidentified Correspondence, undated (Box 66, Folder 120)
  - Series 13, Subseries B: Manuscripts
    - Pretty Redwing (early work-in-progress draft with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Pretty Redwing (marked "early ms" with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Pretty Redwing (marked "early ms" with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Pretty Redwing (marked "early ms + unused material" and "attempt to work in Laundry"), undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Pretty Redwing (xerox copy of pages 168-196), undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Pretty Redwing (marked "wrong turn taken" with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Pretty Redwing (marked "edited version" with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Pretty Redwing (marked "edited version" with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Pretty Redwing (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 1, undated (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Pretty Redwing (unidentified draft with corrections)-Part 2, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Pretty Redwing (first pass galley masters, 7/28/1982), undated (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Pretty Redwing (galleys), undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Pretty Redwing (galleys and book cover), undated (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Pretty Redwing (proofs, 9/13/1982), undated (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Pretty Redwing (setting copy)-Part 1, undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Pretty Redwing (setting copy)-Part 2, undated (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Flora (notes), undated (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Flora (early work-in-progress draft with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Flora (marked "second copy" with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Flora (early work-in-progress draft with corrections and notes), undated (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Flora (early work-in-progress draft with corrections), undated (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Flora (marked "child portion" with corrections), undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Flora (marked "old second half" with corrections), undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Flora (marked "revision of official first draft" with corrections), undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Flora (xerox copy with corrections), undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Flora (xerox copy with corrections), undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Remarks for Carlow College, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Remarks for William Stephen Murphy, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - "This Is Not a Dainty Town; Pick-ups Command the Streets." The Bridgehampton Sun, 9/10/1980. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - "The Ties that Bind Unravel in Gail Godwin's 'Family'." A review of Gail Godwin's A Southern Family in USA Today., undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - "When We Buy a False Flag." The Easthampton Star, 3/15/1984. (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 68, Folder 11)